Kettle and Idols
Next Episode.
Mirei is, and the rest of the voiture teachers don't recommend it so much, right?
Yes.
What? But if it were Ebichu, Mirei would?
Mirei Senpai.
Mirei-senpai.
Mirei-senpai?
Spicy food.
We can talk about spicy food, right?
Please tell her to take me to Nakamoto with her.
That's enough.
Oh, I see. What is it?
Have you seen it? Was that the one that's on YouTube? Of course it is.
How was it?
It was delicious.
I got to try the North Pole.
Wow, that's great. It was delicious.
You're really into it.
You really like spicy food.
What else?
The other one is Korean buldak pokkmyeon.
Buldak pokkmyeon?
Yes, that's right.
That one?
Is that...
Spicy? I don't want to eat it.
It's spicy, but I can eat it if it tastes good.
He's pretty good, isn't he? This guy.
It's pretty spicy. Even among the staff, it's considered quite spicy.
So, you can eat it?
Yes, I can eat it. Right now.
What is the spiciest thing you have ever eaten?
The spiciest one I have ever had was Peyoung's extremely hot and spicy.
It wasn't from the top or anything.
I gave up after one bite.
That's right.
Mr. Takagi from Momokuro ate that one and got into a lot of trouble.
That was painful, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
I see.
Is there anything extremely spicy that you would like to try in the future? Something this spicy?
I want to be able to eat the hottest ever.
The hottest ever... Mirei, did you eat that the other day?
That was 9.
Mirei ate it.
She said I'm younger than her, so I'd like to try it.
I'd like to say 10.
A mystery.
The other day, I reverted to 5 spicy.
Really?
I couldn't eat curry because it was too hot.
I couldn't eat it because it was too hot and too spicy.
Is it harder to eat spicy food if it's hot?
But if I can eat it, I think it's okay.
It was spicy in a way that was different from the spicy food I usually eat.
It was a little bit spicy, so I gave up on it.
Hey, you should go on location next time.
Yes, I would like to go. I want to go.
I want to see how pretty you can eat.
Does your face sweat? Don't you sweat?
I'm doing this job, after all.
I sweat a little.
Yes, a little bit.
How much? I'd like you to try it once.
Fifteen years old.
Does everyone in the family like spicy food?
My father likes it.
My father likes it. I guess it's in the genes.
Yes.
Then, I would like you to be on this show.
I would like you to go to the location from Ojikan.
I'd like to go.
I was still safe when I was working.
I was safe.
This program was provided by Yuya-san, Myusuke-san, Maa-san, Stapler-lover, Nozoe-Mayu Naoshi-san, and Jai-san.
Thank you very much.